所以现在你已经明白了fragment是在哪里使用的
So now you know, where fragments are used and
并且知道了我们将会在我们的应用哪个地方中去使用它
where we're going to use them in our app. You're
你可能会开始问，究竟为什么要使用fragment呢？
probably starting to ask, why use fragments at all?
如果要把UI组件凑到一块儿，难道我们不能只是创建一个
If we want to group UI components, couldn't we just create
View Group或者一个可重用的XML布局定义吗？
a View Group or maybe a re-usable XML layout
当然可以！但是！Fragment的真实能力是超出
definition? Yes. But, the real power in fragments goes
组合UI元素的，fragment可以使activity
beyond grouping UI elements. They allow us to fully
充分模块化，包括从他们持有的应用状态
modularize our activities, including the life cycle events they receive
中接收到的生命周期事件。Fragment是从Honeycomb的时候开始
in the app state that they maintain. Fragments were
引入以解决一个特定问题的。
first introduced in Honeycomb to solve a particular problem. Honeycomb
Honeycomb是第一个支持平板的Android版本。
was the first Android release to support tablets, and
事实证明，去创建平板UI界面
it turned out, the best way for most apps to
的最好方式是将两个或者
create a great tablet UI. Is put two or
多个手机activity并排。举个栗子
more, of their phone activities alongside each other. For example,
如果你有一个手机应用是使用list activity启动的
if you had a phone app that started with a
就像这样，当你点击一个项会
list activity like this, which you then clicked an item
打开detail activity，就像这个我们
would open a detailed activity like this one. What
称为master detail flow的一样
we call a master detail flow. A good tablet
一个好的平板UI界面会将它们并排，就像这样
UI would put them side by side like this.
从功能上讲，点击这个列表上的项，将这个activity放在右边
Functionally, clicking an item on this list, now replaces this
而不是和在手机上一样
activity on the right, rather than starting a new
打开一个新的activity
one, as it would have done on the phone.
不幸的是，Android并不总是支持在其他activity中嵌入activity
Now unfortunately, Android didn't always support embedding activities within
至少在我们介绍了fragment之前不行。
other activities. At least, it didn't until we introduced fragments.
现在如果你看一下UI元素
Now if you just look at the UI elements, you could
你可以思考一下使用view Group和layout构建的
be excused for thinking you could achieve much the same thing
activity来达到同样的事情
using an activity that was built using view groups and layouts,
而不用操心fragment，在一定程度上这是对的
without bothering the fragments, which is true up to a point.
但是，你将传递所有activity的生命周期事件
But then you'd have to pass through all of the activity
管理每一个UI的状态
life cycle events, manage the state of each piece of the
当它们改变的时候，跟踪他们的每一部分的状态。
UI, keep track of the state of each of the portions
并且还要在任意给定时刻记住，
as they changed. And remember, which screen elements were on screen
屏幕上有哪些元素，以此来保持应用状态。
at any given time, in order to maintain app state.
这所有的一切，完全就是你使用Fragment的时候FragmentManger
All of which, is exactly what the Fragment Manager does
替你做的事情。这使你能退后一步，
for you, when you use Fragments. And that lets you
把每一个fragment当做一个迷你activity来处理。
take a step back and, and treat each fragment as though
举个栗子，在activity的世界中
it were a mini activity. For example, in the world
你从一个activity中启动另一个activity，这个事物
of activities, you start one activity from the other, and that
就会在后台的栈中记录下来。所以，点击返回按钮，
transaction is recorded on the back stack. So, hitting the
我们将撤销那个事物并且将第一个activity
Back button, we'll undo that transaction and bring the first activity
放置在前面。而现在可以用fragment transaction
to the front. Now the same thing can
实现同样的事情。在这个例子中，
happen with fragment transactions. In this case, rather
你不必开始一个新的activity，我们只需要
than starting a new activity, we simply replace
用detail activity替换list activity。
the list fragment with the detail fragment. And then
然后返回按钮会撤销这个事物并反过来。
the back button will undo that transaction and
所以，在理论上来说，你真的可以
reverse it. So in theory, you can really take
把所有使用多个Activity做的事情换成
any act with multiple activities and replace it
用持有多个Fragment的单一Activity来实现。
with a single activity that's host to multiple fragments.